

## Komal Gosavi SR. HRBP

Komal.gosavi4@gmail.com

Sukhsagar Nagar, Katraj Pune - 411046

+91-9527115231

linkedin.com/in/komal-gosavib80298141

### PROFILE

A dedicated and experienced Human Resource professional with over 6.5 years of working experience in the areas of Recruitment, Employee Relations, Employee Life-cycle, Performance Management, Grievance handling, Employee Engagement, Formulation and implementation of various HR processes and policies. Proven track record of successfully reducing employee attrition rate and improving employee satisfaction and workplace environment.

## \* ROLES & RESPONSIBILITIES

- Experience in handling the complete Recruitment Lifecycle, i.e. from identifying recruitment needs to sourcing to screening, till the onboarding of new hires. Also, documenting and updating job descriptions based on requirements.
- Proven experience with Headhunting, Lateral hiring and Bulk hiring for both IT and Non-IT profiles.
- Organized and led campus recruitment drives.
- Preparing and releasing various Employment-related documents.
- Proven experience in handling the entire Employee Lifecycle solely.
- Conducting new hire Onboarding process and oversaw the ongoing training too by keeping track of their 90-day tasks, training modules and other related tasks.
- Experience in handling Generalist and Operations level activities like Employee Relations, Employee Engagement, Handling Employee Grievances or queries, Performance Management, etc.
- Conducting monthly and quarterly feedback surveys, One-on-One Meetings with employees and departmental managers, and tracking quarterly reviews to improve the workplace environment and increase employee satisfaction.
- Reduced Employee Attrition rate by developing strategies to improve employee satisfaction.
- Experience in successfully designing and implementing a few processes like the Recruitment process, Onboarding process, Employee Engagement program, HR processes, Rewards & Recognition program, and HR Dashboard.
- Hands-on experience working on KEKA HRMS Software Knowledge of Payroll processing.
- Coordinated with PF Consultant Team for Compliance related tasks.
- Coordinated and arranged employee Training & Development program.
- Reporting to the Owners and Directors directly.
- Conducting Employee Engagement activities like Team-Building fun activities, arranging company trips and sports, festive celebrations, etc.

### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

06/2023 – present Revnomix Solutions - Leading Hotel Data Analytics & Revenue

Pune Management Company (On Payroll of Executive 81)

SR.HRBP

11/2019 – 06/2022 **Miscos Technologies** 

Pune HR Executive

06/2018 – 03/2019 Suntel Global Pvt. Ltd.

Pune HR Executive

05/2016 - 03/2018 **Skillkraft Solutions** 

Pune HR Executive

### **EDUCATION**

2016 **MBA - HR** 

Pune Sinhgad Business School (SBS)

2014 **BBA - HR** 

Pune Marathwada Mitra Mandal Commerce College (MMCC)

2011 **HSC** Pune NMV

2009 **SSC** 

Pune Vishwakarma Vidyalaya (VIT)

## SKILLS

### **MANANGEMENT SKILLS**

- Persistent
- Proactive
- Determinant
- Adaptability
- Time Management

#### **HR SKILLS**

- Recruitment
- Employee Lifecycle
- Employee Relations
- Employee Engagement
- Performance Management
- Employee Grievances

## **CERTIFICATES**

 $\textbf{Advance Diploma in HR Generalist Functions} \\ - \texttt{Professional Training and Practical Exposure - As} \\$ 

Management Trainee at Métier | HR Services

# \* PERSONAL DETAILS

Date of Birth: 13th January, 1994 Husband Name: Himanshu Bharati

Marital Status: Married

Languages Known: Hindi, English, Marathi

Location: Pune

Date: